Csombordi Rajmund

Software Developer; Bioinformatician

+36 30-4410241 rajmundcsombordi@gmail.com







linked.in/rajmundcsombordi angel.co/u/oboforty github/oboforty oboforty.pythonanywhere researchgate/rajmund csombordi

Senior software developer with a diverse array of domain experience with a focused insight on architecture, networking and databases. Junior bioinformatician with deep experience in toolmaking.

Nowadays I am learning finance & fintech and experimenting microservices as well.

Work Experience



12. 2020 - 03. 2021



10. 2019 - 02. 2020



- Account management system with OAuth2
- Python internal framework build over Flask
- Metabolomics compound mapping & identification database



09. - 10. 2020



- C# .NET Fintech pricing service
- Microservices architecture (multiple teams per service)
- Forex, IR instruments: trading & finances. General finance trainings
- App lifecycle helpdesk & domain-specific IT support for interbank & external clients

Fugro

01, 2017 - 07, 2018



- Geospatial R&D at Fugro's HQ
- Full-stack GIS visualization framework
- C# .NET MVC framework, Entity framework
- Postgres, Oracle databases, AWS S3 object store
- TypeScript, OpenLayers & HighCharts, Angular
- Real-time data sync between offshore equipment & web frontend
- Land-registry management system of the Netherlands
- Machine-learning focus group for GIS applications
- Geospatial solutions workshop

Portfolio & Publications

Key professional & personal projects:

- Integrated authentication and account management system
- Backend python framework built over Flask
- Education document sharing service
- Derivative metabolomics database
- Encryption-based storage app and server
- Online Grand-Strategy wargame



Software skills

C#.Net	Python	JavaScript
AWS, OpenStack	Full-stack web	Microservices
*SQL	Redis	Kubernetes
Software Architecture	Algorithm Theory	Database management
Agile, Scrum, RAD, Kanban	Clean Code TDD	Object-oriente Functional Data-Driven
Windows, Linux	CI/CD	Networking
MVC.Net WPF	Django, Flask, Framework dev	Node.js, express
Nginx, Apache	Laravel, Symfony, Fuel	vue.js, angula react, webpac
Numpy, Scikit	Pandas, R	Matlab
Java	C / C++	PHP
Ada		

Specialized skills

Number theory, Algebra & Vector Algebra	Statistics	Calculus & Analysis
Finance	Control Theory	Machine Learning & Al
Geospatial information systems	Chemical compound databases	Graphics & Visualization
Genome Analysis tools	Population Genetics	Structural bioinformatics
Unity	Game dev	Color Theory

Other Experience

g Geometry Global

10. - 12. 2016

- PHP Symfony frameworks & Sulu CMS
- Web development

GE Healthcare

02. 2016 - 08. 2016

- Software developer internship
- Internal python autotesting framework (for CT/MR/PET visualization app)
- Product merging project: python & bash scripting

Freelance

01. 2014 - 02. 2016

- Web development
- Building web projects for education, accounting and casual landing pages
- PHP Laravel, FuelPHP, Node.js
- Frontend Javascript

Personal Skills

English Spanish Hungarian (novicio) (native)

Domain-specific Business Vision communication Bigger picture

Fail-fast method Empathy Personal Attention

Certificates



MSc, Bioinformatics



BSc, Computer Science



Finding Hidden Messages in DNA (Bioinformatics I)
Genome Sequencing
(Bioinformatics II)